

# Preet Rathi

preetkumarmaheshwari@gmail.com 🔀

03029066394

Karachi center, Newtown, Karachi, Pakistan 👂

preetrathi.github.io/portfolio/

linkedin.com/in/preet-rathi-4aa4b3157 in

live:preetkumarmaheshwari

github.com/preetrathi 🦪

Resourceful Front End Developer bringing in-depth knowledge of latest technology tends to produce clean website design. Experience handling complex ReactJS coding, design, and extensions to meet the organization's front-facing internet needs. Details-oriented collaboration with others to define project expectation and demands. Hands-on testing and debugging to address inconsistencies and maintain performance thresholds.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer(ReactJS)

ZAGOP.com

04/2021 - 10/2021

Karachi, Pakistan

**React Native Internee** CIC Hub

07/2018 - 07/2018

Hyderabad/Pakistan

### **PROJECT**

Blocks Bakery Plugin (04/2021 - 10/2021)

- Currently working on WordPress Plugin (React).
- Created blocks like "Ultimate Addons for Gutenberg"
- Created blocs like Elementor(WordPress Page Builder) basic widget with all functionality
- https://wordpress.org/plugins/blocks-bakery/

Dosage Prediction Using Machine Learnig (12/2020)

- Final Year Project
- It takes some parameters like symptoms of disease, age, and gender from user.
- Predict disease basis on those symptoms using Machine Learning Algorithms
- Recommend medicine for that disease with excat dosage using some medical formulas

## **EDUCATION**

O B.E in Computer Systems Engineering
Mehran University of Engineering and
Technology/Jamshoro

11/2016 - 12/2020

Jamshoro, Pakistan

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript OOP ReactJS

Plugin Development (React) React Native

MySQL Redux HTML & CSS

## **ABILITIES**

Created mobile applications based on React.

Converted design assets into components-based HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Created and updated re-usable code libraries to streamline WordPress development cycle.

Leveraged strong understanding of WordPress core manipulate admin and theme component

Provided front-end website development using WordPress.

# **PROJECTS**

Worked on WordPress Plugin (React). In this plugin, we created blocks like "Ultimate Addons for Gutenberg" and all functionality of Elementary Page Builder.

https://wordpress.org/plugins/blocks-bakery/

#### **INTERESTS**

Travelling Reading Coding